http://teddingtonsystems.co.uk/privacy-policy

Capabilities and ServicesSector ExpertiseProducts and Parts
ElectronicsHardware designSoftware / firmware designPrototypingContract Electronics ManufacturingIRISmodular™Appliance ControlsDesign & developmentManufactureProductsValve FabricationDesign & DevelopmentManufactureProducts
Defence & AerospaceTransport & AutomotiveUtilities & power generationProperty & Facilities ManagementHVAC
HVACGasOilSolid FuelWaterEngine ProtectionConsumer Products
Menu
Home
About Us
About Us
Teddington Group Privacy Policy
Core Competencies
How we work
Your privacy
Teddington Group is committed to protecting your privacy and security.
You can learn more about our policy by reading our Business Privacy Notice.
Questions?
Any questions you have in relation to this policy or how we use your personal data should be sent to gdpr@teddingtonsystems.co.uk.
Complaints
You can complain to Teddington Group directly by contacting us.
If you are not happy with our response, or you believe that your data protection or privacy rights have been infringed, you can complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office which regulates and enforces data protection law in the UK. Details of how to do this can be found at www.ico.org.uk
Website cookies
This website uses cookies. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site.
The table below explains the cookies we use and why.
Cookie name
Cookie provider
Expires after
Description of cookie
_utma
Google Analytics
2 years
This keeps track of the number of times a visitor has been to the site, when their first visit was, and when their last visit occurred.
_utmb
Google Analytics
30 minutes
This cookie helps calculate how long a visit takes by collecting a timestamp of the exact moment in time when a visitor enters the site.
_utmc
Google Analytics
End of session
This cookie helps calculate how long a visit takes by collecting a timestamp of the exact moment in time when a visitor leaves the site. It stays for 30 minutes for another pageview to happen, and if it doesn't, it expires.
_utmz
Google Analytics
End of session
This keeps track of where the visitor came from, what search engine was used, what link was clicked on, what keywords used, and where in the world the site was accessed from.
Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit www.allaboutcookies.org.
To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Google Tag Manager
This website uses Google Tag Manager. Google Tag Manager is a solution operated by Google LLC. 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA (“Google”) that allows marketed website tags to be managed using an interface. The Tag Manager tool itself (which implements the tags) is a cookie-less domain and does not register personal data. The tool causes other tags to be activated which may, for their part, register data under certain circumstances. Google Tag Manager does not access this information. If recording has been deactivated on domain or cookie level, this setting will remain in place for all tracking tags implemented with Google Tag Manager.
For company registration details and VAT numbers please click here
Copyright© 2020. All Rights Reserved. Privacy Policy.
